let us see if we can do some full
predication of our own suppose that this
is the original code where we check if
r2 is equal to zero if it is we jump
here and decrement r1 by one
if r2 is not 0 then we continue
increment r1 by 1
and then go out so after if conversion
with full predication
we get this
first
we set predicates p1 and p2 according to
whether r2 is equal to 0. remember that
this one will be set
if r2 is equal to 0 and this one
is set if r2 is not equal to zero so
they're opposite predicates
this one is set if r2 is equal to zero
the actual question for you is what goes
into the predicate for the next
instruction and the predicate for the
next instruction after that and then the
two instructions are add r1 r1 1 and add
r1
r1 -1 so what are the predicates here
also if we assume that this code gets us
a cpf 0.5 without mispredictions
and that the misprediction penalty is 10
cycles then we should do the if
conversion if the branch equals zero
here is predicted below what accuracy so
doing conversion if branch equals zero
prediction is less than what percentage
correct